Guide to the Truman A. Warner Papers MS 026
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series I, Research Files
  - Danbury Scott Fanton Museum & Historical Society, Inc.
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1956-1991 (Box 14, Folder 7-14)
      Newspaper articles contain information on the formation of the Scott-Fanton Museum, groundbreaking ceremony, past presidents, exhibits, events, personnel,
    - Policies, 1972-1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      Policy Sheet covering personnel, Board responsibilities, agreement with D.A.R., and safety rules.
  - Ecology - Danbury - Regional
    Quarries and quarrying-Connecticut-Brookfield; Quarries and quarrying-Connecticut-New Milford; Norwalk River; Plant ecology; Housatonic River; Dams -- Environmental aspects; Fairfield Hills Hospital; Cave ecology; Still River (Conn.); Water - Pollution-Environmental aspects-Connecticut; Vanderbilt Chemical Company
    - Animals, 1976-1996 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Articles on bears, coyotes, deer, raccoons, beaver, snakes.
    - Birds, 1973-1994 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      Articles on eagles, Canadian geese, wild turkeys, and miscellany.
    - Caves, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      Regional mines and caves.
    - Dams, 1984-1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      Articles on dams in Danbury; and few on other local dams.
    - Fairfield Hills Hospital, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      Proposed usage of Fairfield Hills "campus."
    - Fills Earthwork, 1927-1996 (Box 14, Folder 21-23)
      Danbury landfill development in Beaver Brook area; illegal dumping; Automated Waste Disposal; possible racketeering; federal and state issues of landfills; closing and stench of mid-1990s. Several articles of 1927 when landfill moved to Beaver Brook. Booklet: Connecticut Area Wide Waste Treatment Management Planning Program: 208 Work Plan Summary.
    - Gypsy Moths, 1972-1992 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      The gypsy moth infestations of the region.
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, 1986-1996 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      Principal coverage of Vanderbilt Chemical site, Bethel.
    - Iroquois Gas Transmission System Consortium, 1986-1996 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      The installation of the Iroquois natural gas pipeline through Western Connecticut. See also: Energy and Evolution of Danbury.
    - Quarrying, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      Quarries in Brookfield and New Milford.
    - Recycling (Waste, etc.), 1971-1995 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      History of recycling systems in various towns.
    - Refuse and Refuse Disposal, 1964-1995 (Box 14, Folder 29-31)
      Attempts to establish an incinerator for trash disposal. Also, other aspects of disposal.
    - Rivers, 1979-1996 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      Housatonic River, Norwalk River, and Still River.
    - Roads, 1987-1996 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      Local aspects with emphasis on the Route 7 change.
    - Sewerage, 1970-1996 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      Interaction of Danbury with local towns for sewer connections.
    - Sewerage, Brookfield, 1972-1984 (Box 14, Folder 35-36)
      Attempts by town of Brookfield to move from septic to sewers.
    - Trees, 1984-1995 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      Diseases and pests of trees and maintenance of old trees.
    - Waste Management, Inc. (New Milford), 1967-1996 (Box 14, Folder 38-39)
      History of the development of the landfill in New Milford, the struggle between Waste Management and the city for removal of illegally high trash heap in the 1990s.
    - Water Supply, 1949-1996 (Box 14, Folder 40-45)
      Focus is on Danbury's water supply. See also Student Research Paper #12: Water as a Utility in Danbury, Connecticut, by August F. Serra, and #324: The Quality of Water in the Danbury Area by John Kaltschnee.
    - Water Quality Management, 1976-1980 (Box 14, Folder 46-47)
      Maps and reports from the Housatonic Valley Council regarding aquifers, water resource management, and relationships of industrial growth to water quality.
    - Weather, 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 48)
      Various articles on regional weather plus some of Dr. Mel's Hartford Courant columns.
    - Wetlands, 1986-1996 (Box 14, Folder 49)
      Aspects of regional wetland concerns and legalities.
  - Energy and Evolution of Danbury
    Fuelwood - Connecticut; Gasoline - Environmental aspects; Hydroelectric power plants - Connecticut; Natural gas pipelines - Connecticut; Natural gas pipelines - Environmental aspects - United States; Northeast Solar Energy Center; Power resources - Connecticut; Refuse and refuse disposal - Connecticut; Renewable energy sources; Solar energy - Connecticut; Water use - Connecticut; Wind power
    - Algonquin Pipeline, 1950-1993 (Box 14, Folder 50)
      Articles on public views and protests on pipeline.
    - Animal Power, 1981, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 51)
      Research notes from Energy and Society by Fred Cottrell.
    - Coal, 1971-1984 (Box 14, Folder 52-53)
      Research notes on the coal industry; coal energy as alternative to nuclear and oil.
    - Electric Power, 1958-1996 (Box 14, Folder 54-58)
      Connecticut Impact Studies, FLEC, PUC, PFEC, CCA, cables, rights of way, high power lines.
    - Gasoline, 1967-1996 (Box 15, Folder 2-5)
      Clippings, research notes on energy source, gas crunch, gas lines, and social effects. No folder 1 (replaced with folder 6?)
    - Geothermal Energy (Earth Heat), 1970-1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Articles discuss possible use of earth's own heat as a source of energy.
    - Hydro Plants - CL&P, NU Dams - 1952-1982, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Research notes on Rocky River Power Plant, Bulls Bridge, Shepaug & Stevenson Dams, Penstocks, DPA, HPS (Housatonic Pub Service), CL&P, CLDA (Candlewood Lake Defense Associates), FPA. See also: Truman Warner Papers: Still River
    - Iroquois Pipeline, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      History of Iroquois Pipeline, protests, disputes with local towns.
    - Iroquois Pipeline, 1990-1996 (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
      Opposition to pipeline route along Still River watershed. OSHA EPA, FERC, local towns.
    - Kerosene, 1858-1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      Personal notes, clippings, alternative energy use.
    - Natural Gas, 1935-1992 (Box 15, Folder 12-13)
      Personal notes on the North East and Alaska Pipelines. Energy and Evolution of Danbury (continued)
    - Northeast Solar Energy Center, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
      Newsletter: The NESEC Update.
    - Peat, 1974-1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      Peat as fuel source.
    - Petroleum-Gas-Alcohol, 1940-1984 (Box 15, Folder 17-22)
      Research notes on OPEC, oil dependency and economic effects of oil consumption, Alaska pipeline, Exxon Valdez, oil profits, and politics. See also: Gasoline folder.
    - Power Grid, 1957-1982 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      Power grids, PUCA, microwave problems, power lines.
    - Solar Energy, 1972-1984 (Box 15, Folder 24-28)
      All aspects of solar heating as alternative energy source.
    - Wind Power, 1971-1982 (Box 15, Folder 29-30)
      "Wind Energy for Human Needs" by Marshall F. Merriam in Technology Review 1977. Wind power as an energy source.
    - Wood Fuel-Charcoal, 1973-1982 (Box 15, Folder 31-33)
      Energy crisis, state firewood program, cutting permits, tree poaching, economics of wood fuel.
  - Farming
    Agricultural conservation -- Connecticut; Agriculture -- Connecticut; Tobacco farming - Connecticut - Economic conditions; Ecology; Dairy farms -- Connecticut; Blue Jay Orchards; Orchards - Connecticut; Land use, Rural - Connecticut; Farms - Connecticut - Preservation; Tobacco farms - Connecticut; Soil conservation - Connecticut
    - Agriculture, 1960-1989 (Box 15, Folder 34-36)
      Articles on the changes in Connecticut's agricultural policies and farm economics. Decline in dairy but an in crease in chickens, sheep, mushroom, horticulture, nurseries, organic farming and the humus business. Statistics of farms closing n Fairfield County and Conn. Farm Preservation Program to ensure land stays agricultural use.
    - Dairy Farming, 1879-1996 (Box 15, Folder 37)
      Local articles on vanishing open space, dairy industry, farm economy, and loss of dairy farms locally and in Connecticut. See also Student Research Paper #35: Dairy Farming in Danbury Since 1920 by J. V. Edwards.
    - Domesticated Animals, 1960-1984 (Box 15, Folder 38)
      Research notes and clippings on animal husbandry in local area farms.
    - Ecology-Farms, Plant Growth, 1781-1996 (Box 15, Folder 39-44)
      Articles and research material concern the history and evolution of farming in Connecticut, which include energy sources, crop distribution and land use. Pamphlet: Early American Soil Conservationists.
    - Farming-Early Conditions, Social Life, etc., 1941-1996 (Box 15, Folder 45-50)
      Clippings, personal research notes, correspondence, bulletins on the general history of farming and farming practices in Connecticut from the 17th century to the present. Booklets: Land, Bread, and History; A Research Report on the Potential for Food Self-Sufficiency in Vermont, 1976; The History of Land Use in the Harvard Forest by Hugh M. Raup and Reynold E. Carlson, 1941; The View From John Sanderson's Farm: A Perspective for the Use of the Land by Hugh M. Raup, 1966.
    - Farming-Area Notes, 1600-1983, undated (Box 15, Folder 51-53)
      This file is a composite study/history on farming and agriculture for a research/lecture project. The research material covers years 1600 to current day. The theme is change and the effects of industrialization on farming and agriculture in the Connecticut and Still River Valleys from railroads to machinery and equipment. Rural economy, farm machinery, animal husbandry, crop production, farmland tax relief, and Local PA 490.
    - Farming, 1977-1996 (Box 15, Folder 54-56)
      Eroding agricultural base and changes in farmland use due to growth of suburbia. Decline in dairy farming, increase in horticulture, nurseries, Christmas trees, wineries. New Pont Farm, Redding Education Center. New emphasis on diversity in farm crops and farming. Growth of agribusinesses and the introduction of the State Farmland Preservation-purchase of development 1978. The Grange Centennial Celebration 1957. Federal Farm agencies, Agricultural Census, 1992. USDA.
    - Farming, 1982-1996 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
      Articles feature local and area farm families and their response to the high costs of farming in Connecticut and Fairfield County along Route 7/Still River corridor. (New Pond Farm-Redding, Burr Farm-Brookfield, Paproski and Sedor Farms-Newtown, Hurlbert Farm-Roxbury, Warrups Farm-Washington, Smyrski Farm-New Milford, Avrill Farm-Washington) Farm preservation, dairy farms, organic farming, compost, manure, flax farming.
    - Farm Preservation, 1968-1984 (Box 16, Folder 4-6)
      Articles focus on shrinking Connecticut farmlands and growth in urban land use, Farm Preservation Bill, development rights, and Blue Jay Orchards. Pamphlets: Where Have All the Farmlands Gone by the National Agricultural Lands Study, 1979; Legacy for the Future; A Dialogue on American Agriculture by the U. S. Department of Agriculture, 1979; Vanishing Land by the Connecticut Conservation Association, 1974.
    - Orchards-Cider, Maple Syrup, etc., 1881-1986 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Articles on local orchards.
    - Plants, Vegetables, Berries, 1963-1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      Clippings covering topics such as old Indian herbs and herbal remedies, wildflowers, endangered trees, birds, general flora and fauna, problems caused by suburban sprawl; organic and natural food movements. Catnip Acres Herb Farm, Blue Jay Orchards.
    - Soils, 1982-1986 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      One clipping and several reports on soil conservation, erosion, and percolation tests for the Danbury Scott Fanton Museum & Historical Society.
    - Tobacco Farming, 1907-1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      Clippings on local tobacco economy and job market, modern economic growth of cigar industry, and migrant camps.
  - Floods
    Danbury (Conn.) -- Flood, 1955.; Hurricanes -- New England -- Connecticut; Flood control - Connecticut - Fairfield County; Floods; Floods - Connecticut - 20th century; Floods - Connecticut - Bristol - Pictorial works; Floods - Connecticut - Pictorial works; Floods - Connecticut - Torrington - Pictorial works; Floods - New England; Hurricanes -- Connecticut -- Pictorial works; Floods - Connecticut - Winsted - Pictorial works; Flood damages - Connecticut - Pictorial works
    - Hurricane Flood, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      A comprehensive photo study of the catastrophic floods that devastated the Connecticut and Merrimac Valleys in 1938.
      Booklets: The Bell System Meets Its Greatest Test by Judson S. Bradley. Reprinted from the October 1938 Bell Telephone Quarterly.
      The Moving Finger Writes, and Having Writ, Moves On published by The Works Progress Administration for Connecticut. 1938.
    - Magazine: Photo Record, Hurricane and Flood, New England's Greatest, undated (Box OS 1, Folder *)
      Disaster edited by The Connecticut Circle Magazine. 1938.
    - Flood 1955, 1955-1993 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      Articles on the 1955 flood damage in Danbury and area towns. Full photo coverage of the damage done by the Still, Housatonic, and Norwalk Rivers.
    - Flood, 1955-1965 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Articles/photos on area flooding. Request by city for government funds to control Still River.
    - Floods 1955, 1955-1985 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      Articles and photos of area flooding and editorials on the need for better flood control. Most articles criticize the lack of good planning and conservation policies. Development of the Flood Control and Erosion Board established in 1955 and its suggested demise in 1982.
    - Booklet: Danbury, Northern Fairfield Flood Pictures. A Pictorial Review of the Flood, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
      Disaster of Oct. 15-16, 1955.
    - Booklet: The August Flood of 1955, A Special Edition of The Beacon issued by, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
      The Travelers Insurance Companies.
    - Floods 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      Newspaper clippings and photos on regional and area flooding.
    - Floods 1984, 1982-1993 (Box 16, Folder 18-19)
      Articles on New Milford floods, Housatonic flooding on Route 7, dams failing, and hurricane damage.
    - Flood Control, 1958-1985 (Box 16, Folder 20-21)
      Comprehensive articles and editorials on Phase I and II of the Still River flood control projects in Danbury. Most of the information deals with Danbury and the subsequent urban renewal of downtown. Many photos of the re-channeling of the Still River by the Army Corps of Engineers and editorials on the use of federal funds/grants policies. See also: Danbury Downtown Redevelopment
    - Norwalk Flood Control, 1964-1985 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      Articles on Norwalk River flood control and the impact on Route 7 in lower Fairfield County region.
  - Genealogy
    Genealogy - Connecticut; Death notices -- Connecticut -- Danbury; Obituaries - Connecticut - Danbury; Genealogy - Connecticut - Danbury
    - Early Danbury Families, 1600-1883, undated (Box 16, Folder 23-26)
      Several newspaper articles, genealogies, family trees constructed by Truman Warner, which include Ebenezer Hickok, Trowbridge, Hoyt, and Short families.
    - A Individuals and Families, 1931-1995 (Box 16, Folder 27-28)
      Newspaper articles and obituaries on notable local and regional individuals and families, which include politicians, musicians, actors, singers, ministers, teachers, critics, politicians, lawyers, and historians. In addition, there are articles on national politicians including Elmo Roper, Alice Rowland, Philip Berrigan, Willie Wolfe, Ted Sorenson, and Mabel Smythe-Black.
    - B Individuals and Families, 1966-1993 (Box 16, Folder 29-32)
      Newspaper articles and obituaries.
    - Bacon Family, 1903 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      Research notes and obirtuary of Mrs. John W. Bacon.
    - Joel Barlow and American Nationalism by T. Warner, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 34-35)
      Clippings and research notes on Barlow commemoration in 1935. Excerpts from book review of Life and Letters of Joel Barlow.
    - Barnum Family, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      Genealogy. Challenger to Eliza Barnum will.
    - Beebe Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
      Research notes.
    - Benedict Family, 1787-1986 (Box 16, Folder 38-39)
      Clippings of obituaries, copies of wills and family history including the charges made in the Danbury Raid of 1777.
    - Burr Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Bushnell Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - C Individuals and Families, 1964-1996 (Box 16, Folder 42-43)
      Newspaper articles and obituaries of local and regional individuals.
    - Coburn Family, 1968-1976 (Box 16, Folder 44)
      Clippings about Rev. John B. Coburn.
    - Conniff Family, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 45)
      Clippings on Andrew Conniff, Representative to Hartford. AP telegrapher Frank Conniff, executive Hearst papers, and editor of the World Journal, 1966.
    - Cook Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
      Research notes and the Danbury News-Times Johnny Wooster column.
    - Curtis/Curtiss Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - D Individuals and Families, 1974-1995 (Box 16, Folder 48-49)
      Newspaper articles and obituaries of local and regional individuals
    - Dibble Family, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 50)
      Research notes and articles on the descendants still living in Danbury.
    - Dyer, James, 1983-1996 (Box 16, Folder 51-53)
      Clippings from the Danbury News-Times. Obituaries of parents, autobiography, charges and trial in 1990.
    - E Individuals and Families, 1966-1990 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Ely Family, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 55)
      Research notes, family tree, and obituary of Junior L. Ely.
    - F Individuals and Families, 1967-1995 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Fanton, Adella & Fanton Family, 1962-1995 (Box 16, Folder 57)
      Editorials, articles, church bulletins, and research notes.
    - Fry Family (Brooks), undated (Box 16, Folder 58)
      Research notes and copy of family record from Bible.
    - G Individuals and Families, 1957-1996 (Box 16, Folder 59-60)
    - Gregory Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - H Individuals and Families, 1938-1995 (Box 16, Folder 62-64)
    - Hamilton Family, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 65)
      Research notes, clippings, and obituaries.
    - Hoyt Family, 1898-1982 (Box 16, Folder 66)
      Research notes and clippings on Lawrence Hoyt, founder of Walton Books.
    - Hull Family, 1975-1994 (Box 16, Folder 67)
      Obituaries of John and Robert Hull.
    - Hull, Treat Clark, 1843-1996 (Box 16, Folder 68)
      Obituaries, articles, and letters to the editor, copy of Hull founders (source and date unknown).
    - I Individuals and Families, 1976-1986 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - J Individuals and Families, 1967-1995 (Box 16, Folder 70)
      Robert Jennings discovered Grandma Moses' paintings.
    - Jarvis, Stephen, undated (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - K Individuals and Families, 1947-1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Douglas Kennedy, co-founder of National Lampoon, and Helen Keller, et al.
    - Knapp Family, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Research notes and several articles covering many generations of Knapps.
    - L Individuals and Families, 1967-1996 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
    - Lindberg, Charles, 1941-1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Newspaper and magazine articles.
    - M Individuals and Families, 1955-1996 (Box 17, Folder 6-8)
      Research notes, obituaries and articles.
    - McLean Family, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Danbury News-Times articles and obituaries.
    - Meeker Families, 1949-1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      Danbury News-Times articles on Harold Meeker, Meeker's Store, Genealogy, and the 100th year celebration.
    - Mygatt Family, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      Newspaper clippings, genealogy, John Brewster, Jr. found folk-painter of portraits. Suit over sale of paintings.
    - N Individuals and Families, 1960-1995 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Nichols Family, 1898, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
      Research notes, sources, genealogy, term paper, and obituaries.
    - O Individuals and Families, 1979-1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - P Individuals and Families, 1964-1995 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      Obituaries, research notes, and genealogy.
    - Penfield Family, 1942, 1966, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      Newspaper clippings from the Danbury News-Times on Levi Penfield, tombstone in parking lot but no body. Dr. Sophie Penfield, first practicing women's physician in Connecticut.
    - Q Individuals and Families, 1965-1995 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - R Individuals and Families, 1942-1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Rider/Ryder Families, 1893-1988 (Box 17, Folder 20-21)
      Genealogy research notes.
    - Rogers/Peffers, 1957-1984 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      Clippings and obituaries from the Danbury News-Times.
    - Rounds Family, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      Clippings on Mr. and Mrs. Tom Rounds, Bardens and "Behind Iron Curtain."
    - Rudenstein, Neil, 1960-1995 (Box 17, Folder 24-25)
      Newspaper and magazine clippings. Provost at Princeton; Dean of College, Princeton; Mellon Foundation, President of Harvard. Several articles on local doctors training.
    - Ryan Family (Pat Nixon), 1968-1972 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - S Individuals and Families, 1964-1996 (Box 17, Folder 27-30)
    - Seelye/Seeley Family, 1886-1939 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      Newspaper articles and reprint of 90 year old letters of Julia Hawley Seeley. Donation of Bethel Public Library.
    - Selleck Family, 1829-1941 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      Genealogy, newspaper clippings/obituaries, and copies of family records.
    - Seymour Family, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
      Research notes and genealogy.
    - Shove Family, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Starr Family, undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
      Genealogy research notes, copies from D.A.R. scrapbook, and newspaper articles on Nathan Starr, John B. and Sarah M. Starr.
    - Starr, Comfort-Family Tree, undated (Folder OS Folder 9)
    - Starr, Harriet Howard White, 1871-1996 (Box 17, Folder 36-37)
      Copy of letter dated July 6, 1971, written by Harriet Howard White Starr to her grandchildren giving genealogy of the Starr family. Includes several newspaper articles.
    - Stevens Family, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      Genealogy information and obituary of Elizabeth Lynes Stevens.
    - Sunderland Family, 1958-1972 (Box 17, Folder 39)
      Newspaper articles and obituaries. Mayor of Danbury and architect.
    - T Individuals and Families, 1963-1997 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Taylor Family, 1955-1985 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      Danbury News-Times articles and obituaries, and research notes on genealogies.
    - Taylor Family-Stanley Leach Taylor, 1951-1995 (Box 17, Folder 42-44)
      A few newspaper articles and a copy of forward in a book of Stanley Leach Taylor with genealogy dated, 1951.
    - Taylor Family (A Taylor Memoir, Part 1 and 2) 1973-1993, undated (Box 17, Folder 45-48)
      Newspaper articles on 70th anniversary, obituary, copy of A Taylor Memoir by Beth Taylor with photos.
    - Trowbridge Family, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 49)
      Danbury News Times clippings, research notes, and article on genealogy of George Trowbridge family.
    - Tweedy Family, 1864-1984 (Box 17, Folder 50-51)
      Articles, obituaries, and research notes. Copy of John Tweedy and Descendants-1884, articles on family.
    - U Individuals and Families, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 52)
      One editorial on the death of Louis Untermeyer of Newtown.
    - V Individuals and Families, 1967-1995 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - W Individuals and Families, 1895-1995 (Box 17, Folder 54-56)
    - Wallace, Henry, 1949-1981 (Box 17, Folder 57)
      Newspaper articles and obituary.
    - White, William Howard, undated (Box 17, Folder 58)